Dean of Students - Record Group 5 WLU.RG.0005
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Dean of Students - Record Group 5
Date Not Yet Determined
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
Washington and Lee University. Office of the Dean of Students
WLU.RG.0005
x Linear Feet
Scope and Contents
This record group contains materials created by the University's Dean of Students during the course of their job duties.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is generally open for research use. Some materials may be restricted.
- Freshman Orientation Programs, 7 Box (Box 1-7)
- Student Viewpoints and Faculty and Administration Survey (Box 8)
- New Student Guide Book Packet (Box 9)
- Student Scoop (Box 10)
- Miscellaneous (Box 11)
  - Faculty/Administration/Staff survey on the Institutional Effectiveness Committee, 1999-2001
  - Freshman orientation programs, 1970-
  - New student guidebook packet, 2008-
  - The Student Scoop, No. 1 (Winter 2011)- No. 4 (Spring 2011)
  - Student viewpoints, 1991-1998
  - Una vox: the multi-cultural newsletter of Washington and Lee University, 1988-
  - Freshman Camp informational brochure, 1942-1968
  - Memo to Fraternity Chapters regarding the office of University Proctor, 1959-01-01
  - Freshman Orientation Day Planner
  - Office of the Dean website, 2015
    Scope and Contents
    The Office of the Dean created a webpage detailing their personnel, activities, and policies. The University Library captures this webpage using Archive-It.
    Online Access
    View captures online at Washington and Lee University'sArchive-It page.
  - Student Self-Goverance at Washington and Lee, 1998-02; 1 Item